<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Des Preston</title>
    <link>https://des.wtf/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Des Preston</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 18:31:54 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://des.wtf/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Who&#39;s the Best Engineer You&#39;ve Worked With?</title>
      <link>https://des.wtf/whos-the-best-engineer-youve-worked-with/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 18:31:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://des.wtf/whos-the-best-engineer-youve-worked-with/</guid>
      <description>I ask this question in every interview I have with someone who has at least as much experience as I do. I ask this when I&amp;rsquo;m interviewing job candidates and also when I&amp;rsquo;m the one applying for a new position. I don&amp;rsquo;t really care about what that engineer&amp;rsquo;s name is or where they worked. I ask this question because it seems to be unheard of enough that most don&amp;rsquo;t have a canned response and it consistently spurs insightful conversation.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning from the Golang Philosophy as a JS Programmer</title>
      <link>https://des.wtf/learning-from-the-golang-philosophy-as-a-js-programmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 19:43:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://des.wtf/learning-from-the-golang-philosophy-as-a-js-programmer/</guid>
      <description>These are a few ways that writing Go this year has changed how I think about writing JS.
My background as a software developer I&amp;rsquo;ve been writing Javascript since 2007 or so, daily as part of a full time job for the last 7 years.
Golang started to pique my interest around February or March of 2020, almost as soon as things began to shut down because of COVID. It was my intention to learn more even before the pandemic started, so I guess in a way I&amp;rsquo;ve been lucky to have something to keep busy with.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
